{
  "quiz_name": "Hola, Caracola! Quiz",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question_text": "Una manzana",
      "options": [
        "Obuolys",
        "Katinas",
        "Kilimas",
        "Agrastas"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Obuolys"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "La noche",
      "options": [
        "Laukas",
        "Medis",
        "Miegas",
        "Naktis"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Naktis"
    },
    {
      "question_text": " El cielo",
      "options": [
        "Debesys",
        "lietus",
        "Dangus",
        "Ledai"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Dangus"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "Estoy feliz",
      "options": [
        "Esu piktas",
        "Buvau namie",
        "Esu laimingas",
        "Noriu valgyti"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Esu laimingas"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "El libro",
      "options": [
        "Knyga",
        "Medis",
        "Ugnis",
        "lapai"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Knyga"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "El dia",
      "options": [
        "Geltonas",
        "Medis",
        "Diena",
        "Vakaras"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Diena"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "Dos",
      "options": [
        "Trys",
        "Nulis",
        "Du",
        "Medis"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Du"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "El enero",
      "options": [
        "Vasaris",
        "Stalas",
        "Saldainis",
        "Sausis"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Sausis"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "Una zanahoria",
      "options": [
        "Agurkas",
        "Smilga",
        "Morka",
        "Akmuo"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Morka"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "Una piedra",
      "options": [
        "Uosis",
        "Takas",
        "Akmuo",
        "Kelias"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Akmuo"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "Una ensalada",
      "options": [
        "Knyga",
        "Salotos",
        "Banga",
        "Lapai"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Salotos"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "Un pan",
      "options": [
        "Batas",
        "Duona",
        "Ugnis",
        "Ratas"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Duona"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "Unos zapatos",
      "options": [
        "Batai",
        "Balsas",
        "Sijonas",
        "Muilas"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Batai"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "El jugo",
      "options": [
        "Sultys",
        "Vanduo",
        "Oras",
        "Stalas"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Sultys"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "Una mesa",
      "options": [
        "Sasiuvinys",
        "Medis",
        "Stalas",
        "laiptai"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Stalas"
    },
    {
      "question_text": "La casa",
      "options": [
        "Agurkas",
        "Namas",
        "Kamuolys",
        "Uodas"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Namas"
    }
  ]
}

